Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series III: Other Unions and Organizations, 1936-1978, 3
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Iron Workers Shopmen's Local 455 strike support and souvenir journals, 1950-1961, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: International Chemical Workers Union, Local 143 jurisdictional dispute at Lederle Labs, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Metallic Lathers Locals: strike support and testimonial for Israel, 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Office Employes International Union: v.p. George Firth re organizing and assistance with contracts, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Office Employes International Union, Local 153 jurisdictional problems and joint organizing, 1947-1960 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Sheet Metal Workers, Local 28, 1950-1958 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 917 and Joint Council #16: strike support and "buy union", 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Television Directors Guild on Taft-Hartley definition of supervisory employees, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: United Auto workers: Mergenthaler, other assistance, 1955-1966 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: United Auto Workers: engineering contracts, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: United Bronze and Architectural Workers Guild note, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: United Electrical ...Workers, UE Local 456: major strike at Westinghouse, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Other Unions for strike support and assistance, 1951-1967 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Other Unions on support to miners, textile workers, farmworkers, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1937-1979, 4
  - Abbey Industry, Inc.: Certification papers, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Glass Co.: Lost election and unfair labor charge (transcript of JLR's testimony), circulars, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Abbott Glass Co.: Lost election and unfair labor charge (transcript of JLR's testimony), circulars, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Abbott Glass Co.: Lost election and unfair labor charge (transcript of JLR's testimony), circulars, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Acme and Dorf Metal Door Corporation: unfair labor charges (NLRB case); certification, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Acme and Dorf Metal Door Corporation: unfair labor charges (NLRB case); certification, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Acme Steel Door Inc.: Contract and negotiations, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Acme Steel Door Inc.: Contract and negotiations, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation: Organized after 6-year campaign, Aetna serves as a good example of general coverage of company/union relations (1955-1961). Sidney Raphael serves here as company attorney, (see other shops for Raphael as union attorney). The Arnot Marine Division was taken over by Kahr Bearing in 1960-1961; the rest of the company was sold in 1967. (see also 9/49), 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Aetna Steel Products Corporation, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Albro Metal Products: decertification attempt, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Albro Metal Products: decertification attempt, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Allen-Stevens Corporation: unfair labor charge, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Allen-Stevens Corporation: unfair labor charge, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Allen-Stevens Corporation: unfair labor charge, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Allen-Stevens Corporation: unfair labor charge, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Allied Building Metal Industries: industry wide organizing drive; Bridge-workers contract, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Allied Process Engineering, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - American Bosch Corporation: contract, grievances, 1945-1955 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - American Cable Radio, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - American Cyanamid Co.: election lost in 1946; 1950 organizing drive (see also Lederle Labs), 1946,50 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - American Cyanamid Co.: election lost in 1946; 1950 organizing drive (see also Lederle Labs), 1946,50 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - American Cystoscopic Makers, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation becomes American Steel Product Corporation c.1958; litigation before the NLRB and Federal Court of Appeals on unfair labor charge and company's non-compliance with the contract (1954-1956)., 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - American Steel Buck Corporation: [See 11/57], 1953-1967 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Arma Corporation: CIO rival unions (See also 6/12,9/33), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Associated Nucleonics: Local 105 AFTE and its contract, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc.: First election was set aside and second election lost (1950, 1956); shop was finally organized in 1963. The union charged unfair labor practices and went on strike three times (1964, 1966, 1967), the last strike lasting 5 months. See correspondence for union and company attitudes and positions. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Atlantic Metal Products, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Babcock and Wilcox Company: ("financial") Board of Directors meeting, correspondence, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Badger and Sons Company, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Badger and Sons Company; Baker Process Company: personnel list, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20A)
  - August Bellon, Inc.: contracts, report "on Iron and Steel Industry" shows labor costs by industry; contract terminated in 1962. New agreement, 1967, 1958-1961, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - August Bellon, Inc.: contracts, report "on Iron and Steel Industry" shows labor costs by industry; contract terminated in 1962. New agreement, 1967, 1958-1961, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - August Bellon, Inc.: contracts, report "on Iron and Steel Industry" shows labor costs by industry; contract terminated in 1962. New agreement, 1967, 1958-1961, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Brennan and Sloan and Knickerbocker Construction Co.: union recognition strike (Field Engineers' Strike), 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Brennan and Sloan and Knickerbocker Construction Co.: union recognition strike (Field Engineers' Strike), 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories: construction (see also Ferguson) and operating engineers; reports, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories: construction (see also Ferguson) and operating engineers; reports, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories: construction (see also Ferguson) and operating engineers; reports, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Cauldwell-Wingate Company, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Caye Construction Co, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Chemical Construction Co. (see also Ebasco), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - City Steel Door Corp.: unfair labor charges; contracts and mediation, AFTE correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Cole Electric Products: organizing note (see also Empire Switchboard Co.), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Consultants and Designers: Hollow Metal correspondence, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Control Instrument Co., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Corbetta Construction Co.: litigation for non-payment following settlement of the Field Engineers Strike., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Corbetta Construction Co., 1948-1956 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc.: contracts from 1940 until company moved in 1965, arbitration cases before the NWLB and NRLB (early 1940s and 1965), 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Cornell Iron Works, Inc., 1940-1965 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Marble Industry litigation and recognition stipulation., 1940-1945 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Contracts, negotiations, grievances and reports, 1941-1968 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Contracts, negotiations, grievances and reports, 1941-1968 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Contracts, negotiations, grievances and reports, 1941-1968 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Contracts, negotiations, grievances and reports, 1941-1968 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - John Cullo Marble and Tile Co.: Contracts, negotiations, grievances and reports, 1941-1968 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Design Services Co.: Election lost, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Design Services Co.: Election lost, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Devenco, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Downer, Green and Carillo: Election, termination of contract, 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Downer, Green and Carillo: Election, termination of contract, 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - East Coast Aeronautics, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc.: Election won by rival FAECT-CIO (see also 9/75). 1966 organizing lists of Chemical Construction Co.(subsidiary) (See 12/31), 1946, 66 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc.: [See 13/7], 1946, 66 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc.: [See 13/7], 1946, 66 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Edison Concrete Corporation, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Empire City Iron Works: contract notes, correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: Contracts (includes JLR's 1942 report of switchboard manufacturers' negotiating conference) Arbitration files include company takeover (1948-1953) and JLR's weekly reports, 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Empire Switchboard Corp.: [See 13/7], 1940-1954 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Eppenbach, Inc.: unfair labor charge; affidavits, notes, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Eppenbach, Inc.: unfair labor charge; affidavits, notes, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, Inc.: contracts, negotiations, unfair labor charge and Welfare Fund reports., 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, Inc.: contracts, negotiations, unfair labor charge and Welfare Fund reports., 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, Inc.: contracts, negotiations, unfair labor charge and Welfare Fund reports., 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, Inc.: contracts, negotiations, unfair labor charge and Welfare Fund reports., 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, Inc.: contracts, negotiations, unfair labor charge and Welfare Fund reports., 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Fassler Iron Works, Inc.: SLRB forms, strike call and petition to Department of Labor, circulars, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Fassler Iron Works, Inc.: SLRB forms, strike call and petition to Department of Labor, circulars, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Fassler Iron Works, Inc.: SLRB forms, strike call and petition to Department of Labor, circulars, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Fassler Iron Works, Inc.: SLRB forms, strike call and petition to Department of Labor, circulars, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - H.K. Ferguson Company: construction employees at Brookhaven National Laboratory (see also 12/26), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - H.K. Ferguson Company: construction employees at Brookhaven National Laboratory (see also 12/26), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - H.K. Ferguson Company: construction employees at Brookhaven National Laboratory (see also 12/26), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: field organizer reports and circulars (1958-1959); three-year successful battle to prove company restrained and coerced union-supporting employees (U.S. Supreme Court (1959-1962); union loses new election (1964), 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Firedoor Corporation of America: [See 13/37], 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Ford Instrument Company, 1943-1950 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation: (good example of a "typical" shop in the 40s and 50s), 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - A. J. Fritschy Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Fuller-Turner-Walsh-Slattery, Inc.: negotiation; dispute between Raimist, Local 66 and the International president; obstacles in organizing engineers in the building industry, for example, construction of the United Nations building., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Fuller-Turner-Walsh-Slattery, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Fuller-Turner-Walsh-Slattery, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Fuller-Turner-Walsh-Slattery, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Fuller-Turner-Walsh-Slattery, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - George A. Fuller Company: NLRB recognition case, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - George A. Fuller Company: NLRB recognition case, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Gibbs and Cox, proposed affiliation of employees' Marine Technicians Guild, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Gilbert Metal Products: correspondence (OIB contract), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Milton Goldsmith (architects): contracts, correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Gottlieb Iron Works: includes firsthand accounts of layoff: and lock-out of 4-man unit, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Gottlieb Iron Works, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Gottlieb Iron Works, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Grand Marble Works, Inc.: Contracts, 1941-1946, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Charles M. Gray Marble and Slate Co.: Contracts; management uses wartime concessions; other disputes, 1941-1950 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Charles M. Gray Marble and Slate Co., 1941-1950 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Charles M. Gray Marble and Slate Co., 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - C.E. Halback: reauthorization (1946-1948); merger with General Bronze, 1953) (see also Box 21), 1938-1953 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - C.E. Halback: reauthorization (1946-1948); merger with General Bronze, 1953) (see also Box 21), 1938-1953 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - C.E. Halback: reauthorization (1946-1948); merger with General Bronze, 1953) (see also Box 21), 1938-1953 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - C.E. Halback: reauthorization (1946-1948); merger with General Bronze, 1953) (see also Box 21), 1938-1953 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Haller Testing Labs, 1950s (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Harrison and Abramovitz (United Nations construction): correspondence on Field Engineers Strike, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Alfred Hofmann and Co.: Representation; layoffs, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - H.R.H. Construction Corp.: Litigation from Field Engineers 1950 strike; correspondence, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Hygrade Iron Works: representation, negotiations, 1945-1975 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Hygrade Iron Works: representation, negotiations, 1945-1975 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Hygrade Iron Works: representation, negotiations, 1945-1975 (Box 13, Folder 88)